

ABOUT ME

Hi! I am Andrés, an artist working with interaction, digital media, and games. I have a Bachelor in Fine Arts (University of Seville), and a Master in Visual Game and Media Design (Royal Danish Academy, Copenhagen). For the last 5 years I have been working as a teacher and freelance artist, I developed BORE DOME, and I made all kinds of small interactive experiments. I love learning new things, solving problems, and realizing that ultimately, we should be playing. I have a tendency for drifting (as I wrote this I ended up reading about japanese drifting competitions on wikipedia)

INFORMATION

Andrés Cabrero Rodríguez Date of Birth: 05/04/1994		Andres_acre@hotmail.com		+45 81 94 02 61
Nationality: Spain	4	https://www.artstation.com/acre	0	@wasabipizza2
EXPERIENCE				
10/2019 - (Today)	Teaching at the Royal Danish Academy of Fine Arts, for Master and Bachelor students about Blender, Unity, VR, Procedural Generation, Animation, Concept Art, and Art Direction			
06/2022 - 07/2022	Illustrations for special edition of game "Gerda: A flame in winter" (Portaplay, Don't Nod)			
14/12/20-31/12/20	3D artist and technical art for "The Game of Video Game Objects" for Jesper Juul			
03/218 - 03/2019	Illustrator and layout for the book "The Tinderbox" at Aviendo - VAT/CVR No.: 33877234			
10/2017 - 01/2018	Animator and CG Artist for VR project at TimeStory - VAT/CVR No.: 85553615			
PROJECTS				
12/2019 - 05/2022	PC game "BORE DOME" "Digital Moment" Award winner at A-MAZE 2022, Berlin. Game Direction 3D and Technical Art.			
10/18 - 01/19	Mobile game "Traces" i	n DADIU. Art Direction, Technical Art.		
EDUCATION				
9/2017-6/2019	Master Programme "V	/isual Game and Media Design" - KADk	, Copenhagen	
9/2013-7/2017	Bachelor of Fine Arts	– University of Seville		

TOOLS

Unity (Technical Art, logic)
Blender (3D, Animation)
Concepting (2D)
Adobe Suite
Shadergraph, VFX graph (basics, practical)
C # programming (basic, chatgpt helps)

PCG (Basic Houdini, Geo nodes in Blender)
Visual Programming (Bolt, Playmaker)
Commercial (marketing visuals)
Documentation (sharing knowledge and registering process)
Sound Design (trashy beats in Ableton)